{
    "id": "b53ab410235446119a444ecb369a8960",
    "title": "Such And So | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d036a3f8898b4f3a9c282e8089cb0160",
            "title": "Such And So | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is .......................... a lovely woman.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was ............................. a lot of commotion that I could not understand anything.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is .............................. much work to do.",
                    "description": "We use so before much and many.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were ............................... many applicants and ............................. few vacancies.",
                    "description": "We use so before many and few.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so, so",
                        "so, such",
                        "such, so",
                        "such, such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had never seen ............................... much food in my life.",
                    "description": "We use so before such.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is .............................. patient with her students.",
                    "description": "We use so before adjectives and adverbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am surprised that you have got ................................. patience.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am surprised that you have got ............................ much strength.",
                    "description": "We use so before much.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are ................................ sweet baby.",
                    "description": "Such comes before a/an.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "a such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was ................................. an unforgettable experience.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The watch was ............................... expensive that I didn't buy it.",
                    "description": "We use so before a that-clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is .............................. warm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}